I'm Peppa Pig.
[oinks]
This is my little brother, George.
This is Mommy Pig.
[oinks]
And this is Daddy Pig.
[oinks loudly]
[all laugh]
Peppa Pig.
[Peppa reads on-screen text]
[narrator] It is a lovely sunny morning.
Daddy Pig is driving to work in his car.
Breakfast time, Goldie.
[narrator]
Mommy Pig is feeding Goldie the Fish.
Mommy, Goldie isn't eating.
Oh, maybe she's not feeling very well.
Let's phone Dr. Hamster the Vet.
[phone ringing]
Dr. Hamster the Vet speaking.
[Mommy Pig] Hello, Dr. Hamster.
Goldie the Fish is not eating.
And she looks sad.
Oh, you'd better bring Goldie
to see me right away.
Oh. Daddy took the car.
How do we get to the vet?
We can take the bus.
Oh, goody.
[narrator] This is the bus stop.
The timetable says the next bus
will be here at 10:00.
What time is it now?
Ten o'clock.
-Hooray!
[laughing]
How many tickets?
-One mommy ticket and two little piggies.
-And one fish, please.
The fish goes free.
[laughing]
Hold tight.
[narrator]
Mr. Bull is waiting for the bus.
Moo!
One ticket to the music shop, please.
Hello, Mr. Bull.
We're taking Goldie to the vet.
Oh, dear.
Feeling poorly, are we, Goldie?
She can't talk. She's a fish.
Of course.
Uh, maybe she'd like to hear a tune
on my tuba?
[honking]
It sounds funny.
That's why I'm going to the music shop
to get it mended.
Ooh!
[narrator] Mrs. Sheep, Mrs. Cat, Mr. Zebra
and Madame Gazelle have got on the bus.
Four tickets to the supermarket, please.
Hello, Madame Gazelle.
We're taking Goldie to the vet.
Oh, is Goldie not well?
She likes you.
The wheels on the bus
Go round and round
Round and round, round and round
The wheels on the bus
Go round and round
All day long
[laughing]
Supermarket.
Bye.
Music shop.
Last stop, the vet.
[narrator]
The vet helps sick pets get better.
[squawking and croaking]
Aw. Is this the sad little fish
that won't eat?
Yes. Watch this.
-[narrator] Goldie has eaten the food.
-Oh, she didn't eat at home.
Maybe Goldie was bored at home.
The interesting journey
has cheered her up.
Oh!
You have a very healthy, happy fish.
She's lovely.
Thank you, Dr. Hamster.
[narrator] Mommy Pig, Peppa and George
are going home on the bus.
Mr. Bull is going home
with his mended tuba.
It's as good as new.
[playing notes]
[laughing]
[narrator] Madame Gazelle and her friends
are going home with their shopping.
I see Goldie the Fish is happy again.
Yes. It was the bus ride
that made her better.
The fish in the bowl swims round and round
Round and round, round and round
All day long
[all laughing]
Hello. Where have you been?
We took Goldie to the vet,
and now she's better.
[coughing]
[narrator] Oh, dear, Goldie has a cough.
We should take Goldie
to the vet again tomorrow.
-I can drive you in the car.
-No, Daddy.
We want to go on the bus. It's fun.
Okay. We'll go on the bus.
Hooray!
[narrator] Everyone loves going on
the bus, especially Goldie the Fish.
[Peppa reads on-screen text]
[narrator] Today, Peppa and her family
have come to the Funfair.
I love the Funfair.
Slidey, slidey.
[Daddy Pig]
George wants to go on the helter-skelter.
-Okay, see you later.
-See you later.
Roll up, roll up.
Hook a duck and win a giant teddy.
-Mommy, can we have a go?
-Okay.
-One pound, please.
-One pound?
It's all for a good cause.
Win the giant teddy, Mommy.
I'll try, Peppa,
but I don't think it's that easy.
You're right. You've got no chance.
-What?
-It's impossible.
Waste of money, if you ask me.
We'll see about that.
[narrator] Mommy Pig has won.
Hooray!
That's amazing.
Here's your giant teddy.
Wouldn't you like a little teddy instead?
No way, Jose.
Look, Mommy, a giant teddy.
It's a bit big.
No, it's not.
[narrator] George and Daddy Pig
are queuing for the helter-skelter.
Mm. It's a bit high, George.
Are you sure you want to have a go?
[oinks]
One pound, please.
One pound?
It's all for a good cause.
[laughing]
[crying]
[narrator]
Oh, dear. It is a bit too high for George.
Don't worry, George,
I'll come up with you.
-That's 1 pound, please.
-Oh.
[narrator]
George isn't afraid of heights anymore.
Oh.
It is a bit high, isn't it?
I'll just go down the stairs.
[narrator]
The stairs are full of children.
That's the way down, Daddy Pig.
Oh. Okay.
Whoa!
[all laughing]
Roll up, roll up.
Hit the target and win a giant teddy.
You can do that easy, Mommy.
We don't want to win
another giant teddy.
Don't worry, you won't win.
Women are useless at this.
I'm sorry, what did you say?
It's a game of skill.
How much for one go?
One pound.
[narrator] Mommy Pig has won.
Unbelievable.
Here's your giant teddy.
Hooray!
I want a teddy like that one, Mommy.
They're too big.
No, they're not.
[narrator] Daddy Pig and George
are riding on the Big Wheel.
Hold tight now.
That really is high.
Whoa!
Phew. I'm glad that's over.
Five times round for 1 pound.
Five times round?
Oh, no.
Whoa!
Roll up, roll up.
Test your strength
on the old Hammer and Bell.
What do we have to do?
You hit this button with this hammer.
If the bell rings, you win a prize.
[dings]
No skill involved,
but you need to be strong.
I'll have a go.
One pound.
Bad luck.
Oh, ho.
I'm strong.
I'll have a go.
Stand back, everyone.
Do be careful, Daddy Pig.
You're not that fit.
-Yes, Daddy Pig is looking a bit tubby.
-What?
I'm just saying Daddy Pig
is a bit round in the tummy.
Give me that hammer.
Goodness me.
I've never seen anything like it.
That wins all the giant teddies we have.
Hooray!
Mommy, can we give these teddies
to my friends?
What a good idea.
Thank you, Peppa.
Most kind.
Thank you very much.
[all laughing]
[Peppa reads on-screen text]
[narrator] It is a school day for Peppa
and her friends.
Children, today,
we will be learning all about numbers.
Does anybody know what numbers are for?
Are numbers for counting?
Yes, Peppa.
Who would like to do some counting now?
[all] Me. Me. Me.
Okay, Pedro.
Uh. One, two, three, four.
[narrator] Pedro has counted to four.
Well done, Pedro.
Can anyone count higher than four?
Me, me, me.
Rebecca.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
-[narrator] Rebecca has counted to seven.
-Excellent, Rebecca.
Madame Gazelle.
Yes, Candy?
My mom can count to 10.
[all] Wow.
Yes, after seven,
there is eight, nine, ten.
[all] Eight, nine, ten.
Very good.
[narrator] It is playtime.
Rebecca Rabbit, Zoë Zebra,
Suzy Sheep and Peppa all like to skip.
I like sand
I like sea
I like Suzy to skip with me
[laughing]
I like ping
I like pong
I like Zoë to skip along
I know.
Let's see who can skip the most
without stopping.
I'll count.
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Zoë wins. Hooray!
-Hooray.
Pedro, do you want
to do some skipping?
No thanks, Peppa,
I'm Hula-Hooping.
Wibble Wobble, Wibble Wobble
Wiggle Waggle Wee
Hula-Hoop, Hula-Hoop
One, two, three
Ooh.
How many can you do without stopping?
A million and three.
Wow, that's a lot.
Let's count them.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight--
That was eight.
I'm a bit tired.
I'll do the rest later.
[trumpets then laughs]
Can you do Hula-Hoops, Emily?
I can do them my own special way.
[narrator] Emily Elephant is Hula-Hooping
with her trunk.
Hooray!
I think that was about 100.
George wants to play leapfrog.
[narrator] George likes playing leapfrog.
Leapfrog, everybody.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
Nine.
Ten.
[oinks then laughs]
[narrator] Playtime is over.
[all laughing]
Madame Gazelle,
we can all count to ten now.
Very good.
But we need to be playing to do it.
Of course.
Richard, Edmond,
bring the extra-long skipping rope.
Hello.
I've come to collect Peppa and George.
-Daddy, you're too early.
-Oh.
Not to worry, you can join in our game.
Oh, okay.
-Is everybody ready?
-Ready.
Counting to ten.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
Nine.
Ten!
[panting]
Oh, you look tired, Daddy Pig.
[chuckles]
I'm fine.
I could skip to 100.
Good idea, Daddy Pig.
To 100.
Uh... Maybe to 20.
Okay. To 20.
Eleven, twelve...
[Peppa reads on-screen text]
[narrator] It is a lovely sunny day.
Peppa and her family are driving
to the playground.
Is everybody ready?
Yes, Daddy Pig.
Then let's go.
We're going to the playground
-Ha-ha-ha.
-Vroom, vroom.
[narrator] Peppa and George
love going to the playground.
Oh, why have we stopped?
It's a traffic jam.
But we need to get to the playground.
[crying]
Don't worry, George.
The traffic is moving again.
Stop.
[narrator]
Mr. Bull has stopped the traffic.
What's the problem, Mr. Bull?
Moo! We're digging up the road.
There's water coming out of the ground.
Yes, that's what we're here to fix.
-Ooh.
-Is it going to take long?
It will take as long as it takes.
Digger, digger.
[narrator] George likes diggers.
This way, Mr. Rhino.
Okay, boss.
[narrator] Mr. Bull is the boss.
Mr. Bull, where's all that water
coming from?
It's coming from a broken water pipe
underground.
-How are you going to fix it?
-We dig up the road.
Wow!
We turn the water off.
[narrator] George loves cranes.
Crane. Crane.
We take the old pipe out...
[grunting]
and put the new one in.
Thank you for showing us
your work, Mr. Bull.
Moo! No problem.
Bye. See you later.
[crying]
[narrator] Oh, dear.
George doesn't want to leave Mr. Bull.
We're going to the playground, George.
You can play diggers and cranes
in the sandpit.
And we'll see Mr. Bull again
on our way home.
[narrator] Peppa and her family
have arrived at the playground.
Hello, everyone.
Hello, Peppa.
[narrator] Edmond Elephant and
Richard Rabbit are playing in the sandpit.
[all mimicking engine noises]
Let's play in the sandpit.
-Okay.
Stop.
What's the problem?
We're digging up the road,
and I'm the boss.
Oh.
Is it going to take long?
It will take as long as it will take.
We have to make a hole.
We fill it in...
and the road is mended.
Hooray!
[all laughing]
Peppa, George, it's time to go home.
-Oh.
-Wah!
[narrator] Oh, dear.
George doesn't want to go home yet.
On the way home, George,
we can see Mr. Bull digging up the road.
Bye, everyone.
Bye, Peppa.
[narrator] Peppa and George are looking
forward to seeing Mr. Bull again.
Digger. Crane.
Here we are. Oh.
[narrator] Mr. Bull is not here.
Mr. Bull must have finished and gone home.
[crying]
[engines roaring]
Digger. Crane!
Moo! Stop.
Oh, is the water pipe broken again?
No, Peppa.
This time, it's faulty electrical cables.
How to you mend "ecleckity clables"?
We dig up the road!
Hooray!
[narrator] Peppa and George love it
when Mr. Bull digs up the road.
Everyone loves it
[horns honking]